http://www.wimpy.co.za/privacy-policy/

Order OnlineSIZZLING NEWSFRANCHISINGCONTACT USPROMOTIONSHOMEWIMPY REWARDSMENUHALAAL MENUKIDSLOCATORABOUT USPARTNERSHIPSCLASSIC DOWNLOADTAKEAWAY DOWNLOADMENULUNCHDESSERTDRINKS SWEET CHILLI MAYO DOUBLE CHEESEBURGER & CHIPS CHEESE GRILLER LOADED BREAKFAST KIDS KIDS PROMO LEARN & PLAY PARTY ENQUIRY KIDS MENUKIDS HALAAL MENUENGEN SUMMER CAMPAIGNREACH FOR A DREAMEBUCKSDISCOVERY INSURESIZZLING NEWSOUR COFFEE CREDENTIALSOUR STORY MENUMENUBREAKFASTLUNCHDRINKSDESSERTSHALAAL MENUBREAKFASTLUNCHDRINKSDESSERTSPROMOTIONS SWEET CHILLI MAYO DOUBLE CHEESEBURGER & CHIPS CHEESE GRILLER LOADED BREAKFAST PARTNERSHIPSENGEN SUMMER CAMPAIGNREACH FOR A DREAMEBUCKSDISCOVERY INSUREMOMENTUM MULTIPLYWIMPY REWARDSABOUT USSIZZLING NEWSOUR COFFEE CREDENTIALSOUR STORYKIDSKIDS PROMO
LEARN & PLAYMENUHALAAL MENUPARTY ENQUIRYLOCATORCONTACT USFRANCHISINGMENU(current)HALAAL MENUPROMOTIONSLOCATOROUR STORYPARTNERSHIPSSIZZLING NEWSFRANCHISINGKIDSCONTACT US Privacy PolicyWIMPY PRIVACY POLICYWIMPY PRIVACY POLICYThe term “Personal Information” referred herein shall bear the same meaning as that contained in the Protection of Personal Information Act 4 of 2013 (“POPI”).INFORMATION COLLECTEDPersonal Information may be collected electronically, stored and used in accordance with POPI. If you are not in agreement that your Personal Information may be collected and/or stored and/or used, then please refrain from accessing and/or registering and/or making use of our website and/or App and/or joining Wimpy Rewards. You will be required to confirm your acceptance that your Personal Information may be collected and/or stored and/or used within the Wimpy App. The Personal Information that will be collected from you and stored and/or used includes but is not limited to the following:-First name and surname;Address;Area and postal code;E-mail address;User name;Gender;Contact details;Social Media Accounts and user names; andPersonal PreferencesChildren’s namesChildren’s date of birth.How and What is the Personal Information Used for?Personal Information can be collected from you when you register on our website or when you enter any of our competitions online or when you complete a survey online. Such Personal Information enables you to make use of our App and/or website, to locate and communicate with the registered users of our App and/or website, to communicate with us directly and us with you, and assists us in registering users to our App and/or website.. The Personal Information allows us to monitor the amount of registered users which we have, determine growth in the use of our App and website.Sharing of Personal InformationPersonal Information may be shared between Companies within Famous Brands Limited, including but not limited to, affiliates, subsidiaries, associates, franchisees, business partners, agents and suppliers, only in accordance with this Agreement and for purposes relating to this Agreement.NotificationsShould any other entity request access to your Personal Information, your prior consent shall be obtained before passing your Personal Information onto these entities. Such requests will be for marketing, promotion or competition purposes only. You shall always retain the right to refuse to receive such communications.Any legal requirement to pass on your Personal Information will be adhered to at all times. We confirm that your Personal Information will not be sold to any third party.Whilst every attempt is made to ensure that all third parties and entities with whom we contract, are reputable, we are not responsible for the policies and practices of such third parties and entities, including those within Famous Brands Limited.All communication made by you to Wimpy via the App and/or website, be it positive or negative, requires the submission of your Personal Information for verification and record purposes.ChildrenPersonal Information of Children under the age of 16 years is only collected and retained by Wimpy in the event that a parent or guardian has specifically opted into Wimpy Kids for their child. Such Personal Information will be collected and retained by Wimpy for membership into Wimpy Kid. Wimpy will never directly communicate with a child, however such communications will be sent directly to the relevant parent or guardian.Validity of Personal InformationIt is your responsibility to update the Personal Information provided by you to Wimpy, in the event that same has changed or needs to be updated. Wimpy cannot be held responsible for any out dated Personal Information which you have provided.In the event that any Personal Information is incorrectly reflected on the App and/or website, it is your responsibility to edit your Wimpy Rewards profile on the App.SafetyAs the App and/or website is accessed by means of your username and password, it is your responsibility to keep your password safe at all times and not to share your password with any third party for any reason whatsoever.TerminationAs you voluntarily provide your Personal Information to Wimpy, you are able to terminate the relationship with Wimpy by deleting your profile on the App. Wimpy will no longer communicate with you in the event that you delete your profile. FIND A WIMPY NEAR YOU Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, a limited menu is available for delivery from selected stores only. Store trading hours will be aligned with the National Curfew Regulations.
